I'm home.
（純一）ただいま
（はるか）おかえりなさい　あなた
Welcome back, darling!
今日は早かったのね
You're home early today.
Yeah.
うん　たまってた仕事が
思いのほか早く片づいてね
I managed to wrap up my work faster than expected.
I see.
そう　はい
はッ？
Come.
Give me your coat and bag.
コートとカバン
Sorry, Senpai.
すみません　先輩
すみません？　先輩？
Sorry? Senpai?
That's no good.
もう　ダメじゃない
橘君は旦那様なんだから
You're my husband, so you're not supposed to say sorry.
すみませんじゃないでしょ
Also, why aren't you calling me by my first name?
それと
まだ名前で呼んでくれないの？
U-Uh... well...
えッ　えっと…
その…
すみません
I'm sorry.
仕方ないな　じゃあ続きから
You're hopeless.
Okay, let's continue.
ねえ　あなた
はッ　はい！
Hey, darling.
Y-Yes?!
（せきばらいする）
What is it?
何だい？
色々準備できてるけど　どうする
I've prepared everything. What will you have?
Will you have dinner? A bath?
ご飯にする？　お風呂にする？
Or will you have... me?
それとも…　わ・た・し？
Me?
《わ・た・し？》
Me
O-Of course I'll have you, Senpai-
そッ　それはもちろん先輩…
はい　カット
Okay, cut!
えッ…
はあ～　すっきりした
Ah, that was refreshing!
Um, you said I could have you...
「わたし」って…
今のセリフ　一度言ってみたかったの
I've always wanted to try saying that.
うん　満足満足
え～
Mmh, that was satisfying!
What?!
Your heart beats pretty fast when you actually say the words.
実際言ってみると
結構ドキドキするものなのね
これは　すごい発見だわ
What a discovery!
〈この前のが
途中で終わっちゃったから〉
The game ended halfway the other day,
〈時間とか気にしなくていいように
と思って　家に誘ったんだけど〉
so I invited her to my house, figuring we wouldn't need to worry about the time and stuff.
〈楽しそうにしているみたいで
よかった〉
I'm glad she seems to be having fun.
うん　何？
What's up?
Well, let's go all out and have fun today!
いえ
今日は思いっきり遊びましょう
オーキードーキー
覚悟してね　橘君
Okie dokie!
I hope you're ready, Tachibana-kun!
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Departure
（はるかの鼻歌）
あの　何か手伝いましょうか
Um... can I help with anything?
橘君はゆっくりしてて
Just sit back and relax.
はッ　はい
O-Okay.
熱ッ
大丈夫ですか？
Ow-
Are you okay?!
平気平気
ちょっと熱かっただけだから
I'm fine. It was just a little hot.
もう少しでできるから　待ってて
I'll be done soon, so just wait a little longer.
分かりました
何かあったら言ってくださいね
Okay.
Let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
すぐに手伝いますから
Yep, I'll let you know.
うん　そのときはお願いね
〈まさか　森島先輩が僕の家に来て〉
I didn't expect Morishima-senpai to come over and make dinner for me.
〈僕のために
食事を作ってくれるなんて〉
Awesome... this is awesome!
〈すごい　何かすごい〉
〈まるで新婚さんみたいだ〉
It's like we're newly married!
ねえ　橘君
はッ　はい
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
Y-Yes?
Where are your parents today?
今日　橘君のご両親は？
They're both away on a business trip.
２人とも出張中なんですよ
帰ってくるのは明日の夜です
They'll be back tomorrow evening.
ふ～ん　美也ちゃんは？
I see.
What about Miya-chan?
あいつなら　お泊まり会とかいって
友達と一緒に出かけてます
She's having a sleepover or something, so she's out with her friends right now.
帰ってくるのは
やっぱり明日の夜です
She won't be back until tomorrow evening.
そうなんだ
はい
I see.
Yes.
べッ　別に違いますからね
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
だからって
わざと今日誘ったわけじゃなくて
That's not why I invited you over today...
たまたまというか　偶然というか…
I guess it was just coincidence... that it happened...
別に　わざとでも構わないのに
I don't mind even if that was the reason.
Huh?
えッ　あの～　それって…
Uh... Does that mean...
えッ？
U-Um, well...
あッ　あの～　その…
構わないっていうのは…
What did you mean by that?
だって　お泊まりするんだから
Well...
I'll be staying over tonight.
お泊まり！
Staying over?!
あれ　違った？
いえ　合ってます　合ってます
Huh? I'm not?
N-No, you are! You are!
Okay, that's good!
そッ　よかった
Th-This is gonna be incredible!
〈こッ
これはすごいことになったぞ〉
Senpai's staying over...
〈先輩がお泊まり…〉
〈ということは〉
Doesn't that mean...
《はい　あ～ん》
Here, open wide!
〈あんなことや…〉
We'll do that...
Does this feel good?
《どう　気持ちいい？》
And that...
〈こんなことや…〉
We'll stay like this until you fall asleep.
《眠りにつくまで
こうしててあげる》
And even that!
〈こんなことまで〉
〈だッ　大丈夫なのか　僕は〉
W-Will I really be okay?
〈今日という日を
生き延びることができるのか？〉
Can I really survive this day?
お待たせ
はッ　はい
It's ready!
O-Okay!
あッ　こッ　これって…
I-Isn't this...
I need to practice cooking more.
料理はもっと勉強しなくちゃね
そッ　そうですね～
I-Indeed...
（紗江）えッ
（逢）今日は家にお兄さん１人？
Huh?
Your brother's alone at home tonight?
（美也）もしかしたら梅ちゃんが
遊びに来てるかもしれないけど
Yeah.
Ume-chan might have gone over to his place, though.
今ごろ男同士で寂しく
Those two guys are probably having
a lonely porno viewing party right now.
お宝本鑑賞会でも
やってるんじゃないかな
おッ　お宝本て…
P-Porno?
（くしゃみする）
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]私　私ホントにモテるから…
I... I'm seriously popular, so...
おもしろ～い
That's really funny!
〈せッ　先輩がお泊まり？〉
S-Senpai's staying over?
〈どッ　どうなっちゃうんだ
今夜は〉
H-How will the night turn out?
〈一体　何が起こるんだ〉
What on Earth's gonna happen?
せッ　先輩？
S-Senpai?
うちになかったから
知らなかったけど　コタツって素敵ね
I don't have a kotatsu at home so
I never knew, but they're wonderful!
こうやって
コミュニケーションがとれるんだもの
We can even communicate through it.
ちょっと…
コミュニケーションて　くすぐったいですよ
Wait...
Communication? That really tickles!
とか言っちゃって
ホントはうれしいくせに
That's what you say, but I know
you're actually really happy about it!
ウリウリウリウリ～
ホントにくすぐったいですって
Take that, take that!
It seriously really tickles...
どう　降参する？
Well? Do you give up?
No way! Here's the counterattack!
なんの　ここから反撃です
ちょっと　ダメ　そこは反則
Hey, stop! That's against the rules!
My history with the kotatsu is just as
long as my age, so don't take me lightly!
コタツ歴と年齢が同じ僕を
甘く見ないでください
Sorry! I'm sorry!
ごめんごめん
降参しますか？
Do you give up?
降参　降参する
I do! I give up!
もう　ひどいよ橘君
Geez, you're mean, Tachibana-kun.
すッ　すみません
S-Sorry.
Since I had a good sweat, I guess it's time to take a bath.
汗もかいちゃったし
そろそろお風呂に入ろうかな
Enbi
え～
What?!
ああ～
美也ちゃん…
Miya-chan...
おばさんみたい
She's like an old lady.
≪（梅原の母）
正吉　お風呂入っちゃいな
Masayoshi, go take a bath.
I can't stop now, so I'll go later!
（梅原）今いいところだから　後で
（はるかの鼻歌）
〈どうする
どうすればいいんだ　僕は…〉
Now what?
What should I do?
〈そういえば　去年のクリスマス〉
That reminds me, last Christmas...
《どうして　のぞきに来ないのよ》
Why didn't you come peek at me?!
〈なんてことがあったからな〉
...that happened.
Does that mean going to peek
is what a gentleman should do?
〈ということは
やはりのぞきに行くのが〉
〈紳士としての
取るべき道なのか？〉
〈いや　しかし…〉
No, but...
〈よし　行こう〉
All right, I'm going!
〈行かなくて後悔するより
行って後悔するほうを僕は選ぶ〉
I choose to regret going over regretting not going!
〈それに　誠心誠意謝れば
先輩なら許してくれる〉
Plus, if I apologize with all my heart, Senpai will forgive me!
〈…と思う〉
I think.
That's why I'm going!
〈だから　僕は行く〉
I-I'll show you!
〈いッ　行ってやるぞ～〉
Ah, that was refreshing!
ああ～　さっぱりした
お風呂すっごく気持ちよかった
The bath felt really good!
それはよかっ…
That's good-
うん　何？
先輩　その格好は一体…
What?
S-Senpai, why are you dressed like that?!
あれ　おかしい？
いや　おかしくないんですけど…
Huh? What's wrong?
N-No, nothing's wrong, but...
It's my mom's négligée.
ママが持ってるネグリジェをね
こっそり借りてきちゃったの
I secretly borrowed it!
I can see various things in all the wrong ways.
〈というか　色んなものが
色んな感じで見えちゃってます〉
〈これはもう
森島・ラブリー・はるかじゃなくて〉
This doesn't make her Morishima Lovely Haruka, but Morishima Sexy Haruka instead!
〈森島・セクシー・はるかだよ〉
さっきからどうしたの　橘君
Why are you acting so strange, Tachibana-kun?
U-Uh, Senpai...
あッ　あの　先輩
できれば別の服に
着替えてもらえますか
Could you please change into something else?
えッ　どうして？
Huh? Why?
Well, uh...
それは　その…
色々見えちゃってますので
I can see all sorts of things...
できれば僕の精神的平穏のため
といいますか
It's for the sake of my mental stability.
その…
So...
そうなの？
見せるために持ってきたのに
Really?
But I brought it here to show you.
〈ということはアレか
見てもいいってことなのか？〉
Does that mean I can look?!
〈それなのに見ないのは〉
Would not looking be a betrayal of Senpai's feelings?
〈もしかすると
先輩の思いを裏切る行為？〉
〈となれば　しっかり見ることこそ
紳士の取るべき道〉
If so, then taking a good look
is what a gentleman should do!
〈森島先輩のセクシーな姿を
僕の記憶に焼きつけるためにも〉
Even if it's for the sake of burning the sexy sight of Morishima-senpai into my memory!
Enbi
これでいいかな？
Will this do?
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
Well, uh...
いえ　あの…
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
うん？
〈どうして森島家が子だくさんか
分かったような気がする〉
I think I understand why the
Morishima family has so many kids.
橘君もお風呂入ってきなよ
すごく気持ちいいよ
You should take a bath too, Tachibana-kun.
It feels really good.
あッ　はい　そうします
Yes, I'll do that.
それじゃあ　おやすみなさい
Well, good night.
ああ…　おやすみなさい
Good night.
〈眠れるわけないよ〉
There's no way I can sleep.
あの　先輩？
Um... Senpai?
うん　何？
Hmm? What?
やっぱり　先輩に下で
寝てもらうのは悪い気がするので
I feel bad about having you sleep on the floor, after all.
もしよかったら
こっちのベッドを使ってもらっても
If you'd like, you can use my bed-
Tachibana-kun.
橘君
はッ　はい
Y-Yes?
私ね　言い忘れてたことがあるの
There's something I forgot to tell you.
えッ　言い忘れてたこと？
Something you forgot to tell me?
Yeah.
うん　私ね
卒業したらイギリスに行くの
I'll be going to England after I graduate.
えッ！
Huh?
イ…　イギリスって
E-England?
それ　本当なんですか？
Is that for real?
Yeah.
うん　ずっと前からおじいちゃんと
おばあちゃんに言われてたんだ
Grandma and Grandpa have been asking me for a while now.
They told me to go to England after I graduate.
卒業したらイギリスに来なさいって
でッ　でも先輩は…
B-But Senpai-
大丈夫
I'll be fine.
今すぐってわけじゃないし
卒業式までは日本にいるから
It's not like I have to go now and I'll be in Japan until the graduation ceremony.
卒業式までって…
Until the graduation ceremony?
Senpai's going back to England...
〈先輩が
イギリスに帰っちゃうなんて〉
〈先輩が進学する大学って
イギリスの大学だったのか…〉
Is Senpai going to a university in England?
〈そういえば先輩
ポンプ小屋に行ったとき〉
Oh yeah, when we were at the water pump shed...
《でも　よかった
またここに来られて》
But I'm glad we could come here again.
《思い出の場所だから
卒業する前に》
We made memories here, so I wanted to see it one last time before I graduated.
《もう一度　見ておきたかったの》
《思いがけず
それがかなっちゃった》
My wish unexpectedly came true.
〈だから学校の中で
結婚式の予行練習とかやったんだ〉
So that's why we had that marriage rehearsal at school.
〈卒業する前に
思い出がほしかったから〉
She wanted to make memories before she graduated...
おい　大将　どこに行くんだ
もうすぐ授業が始まるぜ
Hey, boss. Where are you going?
Class is about to start.
３年の教室に行ってくる
ちょっと待てよ　大将
I'm going to the senior classrooms!
Wait a minute, boss!
止めるな　梅原
いや　だけど…
Don't stop me, Umehara!
But...
Starting today, the seniors won't be coming to school until the graduation ceremony.
今日から卒業式まで
３年生は学校に来ないぞ
Their classes have all ended.
授業が全部終わったからって
知らなかったのか？
You didn't know?
Well, a lot of things happened... so I completely forgot.
いや…　色んなことがあったから
すっかり忘れてた
Hey, are you okay?
≪（梅原）おいおい　大丈夫かよ
（響）それで
私に話って何なのかしら
So what did you want to talk to me about?
私は水泳部の引き継ぎに
やってきただけなんだけど
I'm just here to pass down the captainship of the Swim Club.
塚原先輩は　森島先輩がイギリスに
行くことを知ってたんですか？
Tsukahara-senpai, did you know that
Morishima-senpai'll be going to England?
えッ…　ええ
それは聞いてたけど→
Huh?
Yes, she did mention it.
それがどうかした？
What about it?
Why did Morishima-senpai keep it from me?
何で　森島先輩は
僕に黙ってたんでしょうか
卒業したらイギリスの大学に
進学するなんて　大事なこと
Something as important as going to a university in England after graduating...
どうして　はるかが黙っていたのか
私にも分からないわ
I don't know why Haruka decided to keep it from you either.
でも　それで橘君はどうするの？
えッ？
But what will you do about it, Tachibana-kun?
何も事情を聴かないまま
はるかをイギリスに行かせるつもり？
Are you going to let Haruka go to England without asking her what's going on?
それでも　あなたは
はるかの彼氏なの？
Can you still call yourself Haruka's boyfriend that way?
もッ　もしもし
森島さんのお宅で…
H-Hello?
Is this the Morishima residence-
[TEL]（ジェシカ）ハロー
えッ　もしかしてジェシカさん？
Hallo!
Is that Jessica-san?
Wow, that's right!
ワオ　当たり！
その声は純一ね
And you must be Junichi.
Y-Yes.
あッ　はい…　あれ？
京都観光に行っているはずじゃ
Huh? Weren't you sightseeing in Kyoto?
[TEL]今日帰ってきたの
すっごく楽しかったわよ
I just got back today.
I had so much fun!
[TEL]特に舞妓さんの衣装を
着させて…
Especially when the dancing girl let me try her costume-
あの～　すみません
その話は　また後でゆっくり
U-Um, sorry.
I'll listen all you want about your trip later.
[TEL]え～
森島先輩はいますか？
What?!
Is Morishima-senpai there?
Oh, Haruka?
うん　はるか？
はるかなら　今
イギリス行きの荷物をまとめてるけど
Haruka's packing her stuff for England at the moment.
イギリス行きの？
For England?
Yeah, Grandma and Grandpa are really excited about seeing Haruka again.
[TEL]うん　おじいちゃんと
おばあちゃんが楽しみにしてるの
[TEL]はるかに会えるって
So Senpai really is going to a university in England.
やっぱり先輩は
イギリスの大学に行くんですね
Huh?
えッ？
Um, could you please get Morishima-senpai on the line?
[TEL]森島先輩と
かわってもらえませんか？
[TEL]ジェシカさん？
Jessica-san?
[TEL]ソーリー
それはできないわ　純一
Sorry, but I can't do that, Junichi.
どッ　どうしてですか？
B-But why?!
Haruka didn't really want to go to England at first.
[TEL]はるかはね　最初
イギリス行きを嫌がってたの
[TEL]それは多分　あなたがいたから
That was probably because of you.
でもね　どうしてもイギリスに
連れていかなくちゃならないの
But I have to take her back to
England with me, no matter what.
だから今回　私が来日した
That's why I came to Japan.
言っている意味　分かるでしょ
Do you understand what I'm saying?
[TEL]はるかに会わせることも
話をさせることもできないわ
I can't allow you to see or speak to Haruka.
[TEL]はるかに
変な里心をつけてほしくないし
I don't want Haruka to long for Japan
and it'd be bad if she decides to run away.
[TEL]逃げ出されたりしたら
大変だもの
そッ　そんな　それって…
B-But that's just...!
[TEL]向こうへ行ったら　はるかは
すぐには帰ってこられないかも
If Haruka goes to England, she
probably won't come back for a while.
[TEL]もしかしたら　二度と…
She might never come back.
[TEL]出発は卒業式のすぐ後
She'll be leaving right after the graduation ceremony.
[TEL]それまでに
はるかを引き止めたかったら
If you want to stop Haruka before then,
think carefully about what you should do.
[TEL]どうすればいいか
自分で考えてみることね
これでも結構私は
あなた達のことを応援してるのよ
Don't get me wrong, though.
I'm actually rooting for you two.
[TEL]頑張ってね　じゃあね
Good luck.
See you!
ちょっと　ジェシカさん…
W-Wait, Jessica-san-
（電話が切れる）
ジェシカ　誰から電話だったの？
Jessica, who was on the phone?
ジェシカ？
Jessica?
This is going to be interesting.
おもしろいことになりそうよ
期待しててね　はるか
Look forward to it, Haruka.
〈先輩がイギリスに行ってしまう〉
Senpai will go to England.
〈そんなこと　させたくない〉
I don't want her to do that.
〈でも　じゃあ僕にできることって
何なんだ？〉
But what exactly can I do about it?
The 55th   Kibitou Municipal Kibitou High
Graduation Ceremony
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
（麻耶）続きまして
在校生代表あいさつ
Next, we have some words from
the current student representative.
在校生代表…　えッ！
The representative is...
Huh?!
あッ…
失礼しました
E-Excuse me.
在校生代表
２年Ａ組　橘純一君
The current student representative is Tachibana Junichi-kun of class 2-A.
はい
Yes!
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
O-Onii-chan?
お兄ちゃん？
えッ？
（梨穂子）純一？
たッ　大将？
Junichi?
B-Boss?
（薫）純一？
Junichi?
ちょっと　在校生代表って
絢辻さんじゃなかったっけ？
Wait, weren't you the current
student representative, Ayatsuji-san?
（詞）かわってほしいって
橘君に頼まれたの→
Tachibana-kun begged me to let him do it.
どうしても伝えたいことが
あるからって
He said he had something he wanted to say, no matter what.
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
（深呼吸する）
厳しい冬から
新しい芽吹きの季節へと
Today, we transition from a harsh winter to a season of budding flowers.
移り変わろうとしている今日
輝日東高校の学び舎から
旅立っていく卒業生の皆さん
To everyone who is graduating from Kibitou High and about to depart on a journey...
ご卒業　おめでとうございます
Congratulations on your graduation.
先輩方と過ごした　この月日は
僕達にとって
Memories of the days we spent with you all will remain with us forever.
忘れがたい思い出となりました
本当にたくさんの思い出があって
We've made so many memories that I can't
possibly say everything I want about them here.
とても　この場では
語り尽くせません
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
（会場がざわつく）
高校に入学したときから　先輩は
Ever since I entered high school, Senpai, you've been the girl of my dreams.
僕にとって憧れの存在でした
先輩　覚えてますか？
Senpai, do you remember?
最初に告白したとき　僕
見事にフラれましたよね
When I first confessed to you, you quickly rejected me.
でも　２回目の告白のとき　先輩は
好きでいていいって言ってくれた
But when I confessed the second time,
you said I could remain in love with you.
橘君
Tachibana-kun...
Many things happened after that.
それから　色々ありました
一緒に馬跳びして遊んだり
We played leapfrog together and looked for photobooks of dogs in the library.
図書室で犬の写真集を探したり
女子用の水着持ってないかって
聞かれたときはビックリしました
I was really surprised when you suddenly
asked me if I was carrying a girl's swimsuit.
その後　女子水泳部が練習している
プールに行って
We then went to the pool where the
Girls Swim Club was having their training,
塚原先輩に
２人で怒られましたけど
but Tsukahara-senpai got mad at us both.
I haven't forgotten any of them.
どれも忘れられません
全部覚えています
I remember them all.
だから僕は
先輩ともっと思い出をつくりたい
That's why I want to make more memories with you, Senpai.
I don't want you to go to England.
先輩にイギリスに
行ってほしくありません
はるか　好きだ　大好きだ
Haruka, I love you!
I really love you!
Please marry me!
僕と結婚してくれ！
The 55th Graduation Ceremony
大将　よく言った
Nicely done, boss!
Let's find happiness together, Haruka!
一緒に幸せになろう　はるか
僕と一緒に
With me!
純一…
Junichi...
純一！
はるか！
Junichi!
Haruka!
純一！
うれしい　大好き
I'm so happy! I love you!
もちろんオーケーよ
Of course I'll marry you!
（拍手）
いいぞ　にぃに　カッコいい
Nice one, Nii-nii! You're so cool!
みッ　美也ちゃん…
M-Miya-chan...
やめなさい　２人とも
そんなうらやましい…
S-Stop that, you two!
You're making me jealous-
じゃなかった　みんなも静かに
No, I mean...
Quiet, everyone!
何とまあ…
Oh, my.
こんなことになるなんて
聞いてなかったんですけど　橘君
You never mentioned any of this, Tachibana-kun.
まさか　こういうプロポーズとはね
ちょっと　あおりすぎたかしら
I didn't expect him to propose like that.
He might have overdone it a little.
はるかは１週間
イギリスに行くだけなんだけどね
Haruka's just going to England for a week.
でも　結果大成功
But this was a pretty big success!
おめでとう　はるか
Congratulations, Haruka!
ずっとず～っと仲良しでいようね
Let's love each other forever and ever.
はい　もちろんです
Yes, of course!
おめでとう　大将
おめでとう
Congratulations, boss!
Congratulations!
おめでとう
コングラッチュレーションズ
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
はい　いくよ～
Okay, here we go!
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
（美也）ニューヨークに行きたいか！
（一同）お～！
Preview
Next episode preview.
Everyone, wanna go to New York?
おい　美也！
（美也）むしろ入浴したいか！
Yeah!
Huh?
Hey, Miya!
Or would you rather take a bath?
TL Note: Nyuuyoku (taking a bath) puns with New York.
（一同）お～！
何言ってんだよ　わけ分かんないぞ
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
（美也）それはそうだよ
にぃに次の回　出ないし→
What you're saying doesn't make sense!
Well, of course it wouldn't.
You won't be in the next episode anyway.
男子禁制なんだよ
女性限定なんだよ　当たり前じゃん
No way!
Guys are banned! It's a girls-only episode!
僕　主役なのに…
次回「オンセン」
Of course you won't be in it.
B-But I'm the protagonist...
（美也）ぬっくぬっく
プッカプッカ　いい感じ
Next Episode
Tachibana Miya
Hot Springs
Next episode: "Hot Springs".
Splish, splash, it feels so good!